This is Varsha V. Neal Sudeja. I've recently completed my BTEC in Computer
Science from VIT Willow, and I'm here to explain my Lingman Postscraper,
which I've built using Anatem. So this Lingman Postscraper analyzes
top posts posted by users. on LinkedIn for some particular marketing of
their brands. Uh, after analyzing these posts,
it converts them into a founder-style posts that
will market our brand. So it,
uh, basically helps us get more reactions on our posts and attract people.
So, uh, we start with a manual trigger here.
Uh, once this is, uh,
done, uh, we move on to a Google Sheet that I've given.
So this of,
uh, founders, uh, that market their brands with their LinkedIn URLs.
So, uh, then we move on to this HTTP node,
which connects it with API to scrape the bot.
Once the scraping is done,
it pens this into the Google Sheet,
which is here, uhh, and the same sheet on a different tab.
So, here all the data will be available in it.
Once the data has been appended,
uhh, we move on to the Lanchine's LLM chain,
to which I have given a prompt saying you were rolling and goes right
over a clothing brand. And it has to,
uhh, uhh, take out post into the hook type and hook example
text. And there should be the output.
Uhh, once this is done, it's uhh, uhh, passed using the,
output password, using Google Chennai.
Then again, we use this L&M chain,
almost saying, you were rolling when you go straight off a start-up called Amplify,
which is a premium clothing drawing plan and here is our what should be
the post come with the post text. So,
this will analyze the post given by the last L&M chain and convert
it into a founder-style post,
which is, which connects users and which explains our founder's journey.
So, uhh. This is how it works.
Once this is done, we structured using the output password again
and we finally hope
it will have the original competitor post and the generated post here.
So let's try this out. You
will
see that, uhh,
apofia is extracted dot text.
And then you will- It has appended into the sheet on this format,
which we can see here. So here,
umm, the text,
the creator and the number of reactions for the all the posts.
So we have this data. Once this is done,
we move on to the basic alarm chain,
which gives output. In this format,
like, uh, heading at the text. Using Google Gemini.
Once this is done, the post is being analyzed and converted into
a found-is-type post, which can help us brand,
uh. Once this is done,
it gets appended into the Google Sheet,
that we can compare the original post as it was here.